VISHNU PRIYAN J.

FRONT-END DEVELOPER

CONTACT:

- +91 63690 31601 priyanvishnu15@gmail.com PORTFOLIO(Tap to view)
- GITHUB: https://github.com/vishnu2646

ABOUT ME

Hi, I am Vishnu Priyan. I am a Frontend Developer. My Area Of Intrest is coding and Arts. I am always energetic and eager to learn and easily adaptable to new technologies. I have 1 year of intern experience in Web Development. In Sports, I would Play Badminton And been a Coordinator In Avanta 2020 in College Events.

EDUCATION

2015 - 2016

• Sri Vijay Vidyalaya,Hosur Percentage - 92%

2017 - 2018

• Sri Vijay Vidyalaya,Hosur Percentage - 74%

2018 - 2022

• Sri Krishna College of Technology -CGPA:7.9

EXPERIENCE

2021 TK-HOSUR (FEB 2021 - APR 2021)

MILK PRODUCT APPLICATION

• An Application for The Milk Products Company and Integrated with the Payment Integration (Implemented In Django Python).(Role - Full Stack)

2021 PAYMENTS AND RECEIPTS APPLICATION (MAY 2021 - JUL 2021)

PR Tracker Application For a Deaf and Dumb Association

• An Application to track their Payments and Receipts in Real-Time. (Implemented with Django Python Full Stack)

2021 SEZZLE (OCT 2021 - MAY 2022)

Intern Experience At Sezzle (Role - Frontend Developer, PRODUCT ENGINEER)

2022 Incresco (May2022 - Jul 2022)

Software Developer (Role - Frontend Developer) React-Native

2022 Applied Materials (Aug 2022 - Present)

Full Time Employee (Role - Frontend Developer, Associate Software Developer)

SKILLS LINKS AWARDS &

CERTIFICATES

• Django LINKED-IN

• Python **GITHUB**

• SQLITE3

• C/C++

• HTML/CSS

• Django

• Python

Java

• Data Structures(Basics)

• ReactJS(udemy)

• ReactJS (institute)

• HTML/CSS

TECHNOLOGIES

Django

• Python

• HTML/CSS/JS

• ReactJs

• SQLITE3